<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</defName>
        <label>Mechanical optimization</label>
		<tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>Standardization alone will not solve everything - further progress will require a revolution of efficiency and precision. New standards for optimization, accuracy, and capability will need to be developed. Once achieved, humanity's more wild ideas fall within reach.</description>
        <baseCost>4000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalStandardization</li>
            <li>AdvancedFabrication</li>
        </prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>6</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.5</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_AdvancedMechanicalFrameworks</defName>
        <label>Advanced framework replacements</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>With the advent of optimized design and structural techniques, a wide variety of new possibilities for framework enhancements is unlocked. With greater specialization and higher quality, these frameworks are purpose built rather than generic solutions.</description>
        <baseCost>800</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalFrameworks</li>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</li>
        </prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>7</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_RepairOptimization</defName>
        <label>Repair Optimization</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>Optimization to repair stimulants should allow for significantly increased recovery speed and operation success chance in mechanical units. The quality of these stimulants is comparable to that of glitterworlds' medicine - in this respect, their capacity is not much different from lesser civilizations.</description>
        <baseCost>1400</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</li>
			<li>ATR_MechaniteAssistedRecovery</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>7</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>1</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>ATR_T3Androids</defName>
		<label>T3 androids</label>
		<tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
		<description>Tier three androids are marked by their scale and sheer capabilities. Dwarfing humans at an average height of 7-9 feet - necessary to contain the vast requisite resources for operation - and intimidating in both strength and acuity, these units are clear evolutions of human design.</description>
		<baseCost>2800</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</li>
            <li>ATR_T2Androids</li>
        </prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>7</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2</researchViewY>
		<requiredResearchFacilities>
			<li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
		</requiredResearchFacilities>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_CommunicationOptimization</defName>
        <label>Optimized communication</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>In order to extend the power of the communication network and prepare for a centralized host system, optimization to communication relays and the systems that control them must be developed.</description>
        <baseCost>2000</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_StandardizedCommunications</li>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>7</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>4</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_CoreAssistants</defName>
        <label>Core assistance</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>With the acquisition of proper fabrication capabilities and a strong standardization scheme, advancements in the quality of mechanical parts is now within reach. There is spare space in all androids' heads, primarily for protective padding purposes - advanced specialized chips could occupy some of that space instead.</description>
        <baseCost>1600</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_MechanicalOptimization</li>
            <li>ATR_InterchangeableParts</li>
        </prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>8</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_SurrogateOptimization</defName>
        <label>Optimized surrogate protocols</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>With a great deal of advancement in both fabrication capabilities and protocol optimization, it may very well be possible to develop a method for organics to both become and utilize surrogates. This is a revolutionary capability, but one fraught with moral and ethical concerns. Is this a line that shouldn't be crossed?</description>
        <baseCost>4000</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_CommunicationOptimization</li>
            <li>ATR_RemoteControlProtocols</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>8</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>5</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
        <discoveredLetterTitle>About: Organics and the SkyMind</discoveredLetterTitle>
        <discoveredLetterText>With optimized network schemes, you can now manufacture SkyMind transceivers and receivers to allow organic pawns to use the network. Unlike in androids, these two implants require manufacturing. Installing a receiver in an organic pawn to make them a surrogate is considered murder, and is the only way to download a pawn into an organic body without permutation. Transceivers carry no particular negative consequences, and give organic pawns full access to all the network's features that are available to mechanical pawns.</discoveredLetterText>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_ServerOptimization</defName>
        <label>Server optimization</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>Optimizing servers for space and utility is expensive, but promises to bring revolutionary expansion to the colony's insight generation. Combining storage and generation, these servers could make older models obsolete.</description>
        <baseCost>3000</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_CommunicationOptimization</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>8</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>4</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
        <discoveredLetterTitle>About: Advanced SkyMind Networks</discoveredLetterTitle>
        <discoveredLetterText>The Networked Intelligence may require a persona core to build, but it offers the ability to progress deeper into SkyMind networks and can store and generate simultaneously at far higher capacities than lower networks. Two may connect to a research bench at a time, and offers a small boost to research speed - and is a requirement to developing the technology necessary to understand how to manufacture Ultratech persona cores or a SkyMind Core.</discoveredLetterText>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>ATR_T4Androids</defName>
		<label>T4 androids</label>
		<tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
		<description>Tier four androids are marked by the possession of an AI persona core. The possession of such a thing greatly reduces the need for space and therefore size and weight. While its capabilities do not inherently exceed that of a tier three, its persona core does undeniably confer benefits.</description>
		<baseCost>6000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>ATR_T3Androids</li>
			<li>ShipComputerCore</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>9</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2</researchViewY>
		<requiredResearchFacilities>
			<li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
		</requiredResearchFacilities>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_SkyMindCore</defName>
        <label>SkyMind Core</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>The pinnacle of mechanical and consciousness research, a theoretical supercomputer core capable of permanently storing, saving, replicating, and allowing the full use of consciousnesses is within reach. It is incredibly expensive, but it offers a glimpse of immortality. Acquiring and coaxing so many AI personas to play babysitter and host will be difficult. Finding the vanometric power cells necessary to keep the superstructure secure and isolated may be equally difficult.</description>
        <baseCost>20000</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_ServerOptimization</li>
            <li>ShipComputerCore</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>9</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>4</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>ATR_NetworkedIntelligence</li>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
        <discoveredLetterTitle>About: Building a Core</discoveredLetterTitle>
        <discoveredLetterText>The SkyMind Core is the pinnacle of Ultratech SkyMind networks. A conglomeration of highly advanced but still restrained personae within a superstructure with no need for external power - thanks to internal vanometric power cells - and with immunity to atmospheric or environmental effects like heat or solar flares allows for a safe holding chamber of nigh immortal consciousnesses. From within this vessel, consciousnesses can be stored, transferred, or even duplicated. The infrastructure allows for a single pawn to control a huge number of surrogates, allowing for an almost hive-mind like consciousness.</discoveredLetterText>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef>
        <defName>ATR_PersonaManufacturing</defName>
        <label>Persona Manufacturing</label>
        <tab>ATR_MechResearch</tab>
        <description>Persona cores are highly advanced devices that house consciousnesses, albeit ones that are carefully restricted in most ways. Mired in ethical and moral quandaries, their production is held secret amongst Ultratech societies. Free from the constraints of morality and with the aid of a willing persona, it should be possible to unravel its secrets and allow us to produce more.</description>
        <baseCost>15000</baseCost>
        <techLevel>Ultra</techLevel>
        <prerequisites>
            <li>ATR_ServerOptimization</li>
            <li>ShipComputerCore</li>
        </prerequisites>
        <researchViewX>9</researchViewX>
        <researchViewY>5</researchViewY>
        <requiredResearchFacilities>
            <li>ATR_NetworkedIntelligence</li>
            <li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
        </requiredResearchFacilities>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

</Defs>
