<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<ATR_SkyMindDisconnectionRisk>Disconnection from the SkyMind network while the operation is in progress will result in severe consequences. Memory corruption of varying degree is guaranteed if improper disconnection occurs.</ATR_SkyMindDisconnectionRisk>
	
	<ATR_ResurrectionSuccessful>Mechanical unit {0} was successfully reactivated to minimal capacity. The unit must reboot before returning to full functionality.</ATR_ResurrectionSuccessful>
	<ATR_ResurrectionFailedInvalidPawn>The target, {0}, was not reactivated as it is not a valid target for resurrection in this manner. Targets must be mechanical (AT Reforged settings) and must have an intact core.</ATR_ResurrectionFailedInvalidPawn>
	<ATR_ResurrectionFailedDroneOnly>The drone resurrection kit may only be used on drones or animals, and {0} is considered a fully autonomous mechanical unit!</ATR_ResurrectionFailedDroneOnly>
	
	<!-- Skill Upgrades -->
	<ATR_PawnBeingModified>Skills and passions for: </ATR_PawnBeingModified>
	<ATR_CurrentXP> XP required for next level: </ATR_CurrentXP>
	<ATR_TodaysXP> XP today: </ATR_TodaysXP>
	
	<ATR_InsufficientSkillPoints>{0} skill points are required for this operation.</ATR_InsufficientSkillPoints>
	<ATR_AddSkillPoints>Inject points into {0}</ATR_AddSkillPoints>
	<ATR_AvailableSkillPoints>Available points : {0}</ATR_AvailableSkillPoints>
	<ATR_AvailableSkillPointsDesc>Note: Insight injection is subject to an individual's learning capabilities as well as daily comprehension limits. Passion injection is subject to individual learning capability as well as pre-existing passions. Overstimulation is inefficient.</ATR_AvailableSkillPointsDesc>
	
	<!-- Initialize Mind Dialog/Keys -->
	<ATR_InitializeMindTitle>Mechanical Unit needs initialization</ATR_InitializeMindTitle>
	<ATR_InitializeMindDesc>The newly connected core interface is ready to contain an intelligence, but has not yet initialized one. An intelligence may be imported from the SkyMind if any exist or it may be permitted to form a personality on its own.</ATR_InitializeMindDesc>
	
	<ATR_SkyMindInitialization>Initialize from SkyMind</ATR_SkyMindInitialization>
	<ATR_AutomaticInitialization>Initialize automatically</ATR_AutomaticInitialization>
	
</LanguageData>